Aditya Bhagwat

UI/UX Designer



віо

I am a UI/UX designer living in Indore. With a design certification and a year of experience, helping over a dozen Clients obtain a competitive advantage by delivering great user experiences across desktop, mobile, tablet, and other channels. I am an open-minded and friendly individual with an eye for detail and welcome challenges.

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer

A2tech Brothers

July 2021 - August 2022, Indore (M.P.)

Directly collaborated with CEO and Product team to prototype, design and deliver the UI and UX experience with a lean design process: Research, Design, Test, and Iterate.

UI/UX Designer

Maven Cluster Pvt. Ltd.

August 2022 - Present, Indore (M.P.)

Design and deliver the UI and UX experience with a lean design process: Research, Design, Test, and Iterate.

Self Employed

(Freelancer)

June 2020 - May 2021, Indore (M.P.)

Serving clients with design of Websites, Graphics, Mobile apps, Web app, Logo design, Prototyping, Wireframes.

EDUCATION

Web & Graphic Design

Arena Animation

2020 - 2022, Indore (M.P.)

10th, 12th (PCM)

New pink flower H. S. school. (MP Board)

2016 & 2018, Indore (M.P.)

adityabhagwat30@gmail.com

7047007513 Indore (M.P.)

Focus & Expertise

User Interface
User Experience
Interaction Design
Wireframing
Rapid Prototyping
Design Research

Tools & Technologies

Figma, Adobe XD

Other Skills

Illustrator, Photoshop

Languages

English Hindi Marathi

Social

www.linkedin.com/in/adityabhagwat30

Portfolio Links
Cleaner Mobile App
Dentist Web App